http://www.cdnmedhall.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
English
Français
AboutBoard & StaffTHE EXHIBIT HALLNewsSupport UsLaureatesInduction CeremonyInduction SponsorsNominateMore About Our LaureatesSEARCH LAUREATES BY CATEGORYStudent ProgramsDiscovery DaysMuseum SchoolCMHF AwardClass TripsBoard PortalImportant DatesMeeting Packages & MinutesBoard Governance and PoliciesBoard Contact InformationBoard CommitteesContact UsEnglishFrançais
About
Laureates
Student Programs
Board Portal
Contact Us
English
Français
close ×
Enter your keywords
Privacy Policy
The Canadian Medical Hall of Fame (the “CMHF”) is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of its employees, volunteers, donors, potential supporters and other stakeholders. We value the trust of those with whom we interact, and of the public, and recognize that maintaining this trust requires that we be transparent and accountable in how we treat the information that you choose to share with us.
Defining Personal Information
Personal information is any information that can be used to distinguish, identify, or contact a specific individual. This personal information can include an individual’s opinions or beliefs, as well as facts about, or related to, the individual. Exceptions: business contact information and certain publicly available information, such as names, addresses and telephone numbers as published in telephone directories, are not considered personal information. When an individual uses his or her home contact information as business contact information as well, we consider that the contact information provided is business contact information, and is not therefore subject to projection as personal information.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
The CMHF collects a limited amount of personal information about its donors, volunteers, laureates, nominators and potential supporters, including name, title, address, telephone numbers, email address, past donations and other relevant contact information. This information is collected in order to comply with Canada Customs and Revenue Agency requirements, to provide donors and potential supporters with information about the CMHF’s activities, to provide donors with stewardship information, to provide information about the CMHF’s nomination and selection processes, and to promote opportunities where donors and potential supporters may support the CMHF.
Safe Keeping of Information
The CMHF does not sell, trade or otherwise share our contact lists. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the correct use of information, we strive to maintain physical, electronic and administrative safeguards to secure the information we collect. All information is accessible only by authorized staff and volunteers. If at any time you wish to restrict use of your contact information, please inform the CMHF Privacy Officer in writing:
Email: lfoster [at] cdnmedhall.org / Mail: 100 Kellogg Lane, London N5W 0B4 ON
If You Wish to See or Change Your Information
The CMHF endeavours to maintain up-to-date records. Should you wish to review the information we have about you, change that information, or ask us to remove your information from our records, you may contact us through our Privacy Officer at the address noted above. That individual will ensure that your request is dealt with in the proper manner. Please remember that we may be required, by certain laws, to maintain records for taxation purposes.
Another Notable Laureate...
His contributions to stroke research, education and patient care in Canada are unprecedented.
